Britt Fetterhoff

DATA ANALYST/BUSINESS ANALYST

Contact

Email

pennyandjude@gmail.com

Phone

615.337.2010

Web links

linkedin.com/in/brittany.fetterhoff github.com/pennyandjude public.tableau.com/profile/britt.fetterhoff

About Me

I am a soon-to-be NSS graduate, looking for my first step in the data analytics marketplace. My style is strategic and creative, with an emphasis on relationships. Working in hospitality for almost two decades has helped develop a keen ability to anticipate the needs of others, a strong value of dependability, and an eagerness to learn and grow as a professional. As an employee, I am organized, efficient, and always willing to go the extra mile for ontime content delivery. Don't forget, you're better off with Fetterhoff .

Skills

Excel, Pivot Tables PostgreSQL Power Bl Tableau

Python, Jupyter Notebook, Pandas Market Research

Marketing Plan Development

Education

Nashville Software School, Jan 2021

Data Analytics Jumpstart Data Analytics Bootcamp

Auburn University

English/Education

TESOL Certified

Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages

Data Analytics Experience

Nashville Software School (current) Junior Data Analyst Jan 2021

Attended a five month full time intensive introduction to data analytics and business intelligence processes and tools. Used real data presented by Nashville employers through hands on training on every stage of the analytics workflow. Covered skills in Python, PstgreSQL, Tableau, Power BI, Excel, GitHub, Agile/Kanban process, team projects, and remote work capabilities.

Selected Projects

Capstone

Capstone description and tools used

•

Chocolate Analysis 2020

 Analysed data from the Manhattan Chocolate Society's reviews of 2400 artisan chocolate bars. Used SQL and Tableau to create a story to aid potential chocolate makers in decision making

GDP and Internet Usage Analysis

 Analysed GDP and internet usage from data.un using Python to find 10 year trends and any correlations by creating queries, data frame merges, and visualizations

Other Experience

Hazel Hemp Farms Business Owner (part-time) 2018-Present

- Launched a six acre industrial grow opperation in Franklin TN from the ground up
- Manage employees, oversee the planting and harvest of more than 50k plants, and improved performance to double our harvest for year two
- Utilizing excellent organizational skills to streamline processes in order to manage business operations while attending NSS full-time

Ruth's Agency Project Management, Opportunist, Event Coordinator, Bartender 2011-2020

- Orchestrated hundreds of private events across TN
- Managed staff, provided decor, hired entertainment, and personally hosted guests from around the globe
- Optimized efficiency and flow of crowds ranging from intimate to 800 guests
- Leveraged commitment of network to gain continual business without advertising

AAMS inc. Marketing Manager 2013-2016

- Solely created business opportunities for wholesale parts departments across TN, AR, KY, OK, KS, LA
- Worked with body shops to educate owners and employees on OSHA compliance with aamstraining.com
- Visited 40-50 shops weekly, managed logistics, collected tests, and worked directly with IT to ensure company website stayed efficient and up to date with current compliance laws.

The Standard at the Smith House Private Club Bartender 2011-2013

- One of six handpicked bartenders chosen to host members of the private club on the top two floors of the building
- Gave exceptional service to enhance overall ambiance for member experiences
- Set up and break down for many private high-level political events as well as private afterparties for CMA fest, AMA Awards, Nashville Fashion Week, Steeplechase, concerts, corporate dinners, and many holiday parties for club members.
- Ran liquor inventory and managed bar revenues, ensuring all patrons were billed and all cash properly accounted for